{
  "questions": [
    {
      "questionType": "tf",
      "questionText": "In Java, garbage collection is handled automatically.",
      "correctAnswer": "true"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "mc",
      "questionText": "What is a correct syntax to output 'Hello World' in Java?",
      "correctAnswer": "System.out.println('Hello World');",
      "options": ["echo('Hello World');","Console.WriteLine('Hello World');","System.out.println('Hello World');","print('Hello World');"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "text",
      "questionText": "In Java, what keyword is used to skip to the next iteration in a loop?",
      "correctAnswer": "continue"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "mc",
      "questionText": "Which method can be used to find the highest value of x and y?",
      "correctAnswer": "Math.max(x,y)",
      "options": ["Math.largest(x,y)","Math.max(x,y)","Math.maximum(x,y)","Math.maxNum(x,y)"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "tf",
      "questionText": "In Java, it is possible to inherit attributes and methods from one class to another.",
      "correctAnswer": "true"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "mc",
      "questionText": "Which operator can be used to compare two values?",
      "correctAnswer": "==",
      "options": ["<>","><","=","=="]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "tf",
      "questionText": "Java is short for 'JavaScript'",
      "correctAnswer": "false"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "text",
      "questionText": "In Java, what keyword is an access modifier used for classes, attributes, methods and constructors, making them accessible by any other class?",
      "correctAnswer": "public"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "mc",
      "questionText": "Which method can be used to return a string in upper case letters?",
      "correctAnswer": "toUpperCase()",
      "options": ["tuc()","upperCase()","toUpperCase()","touppercase()"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "mc",
      "questionText": "How do you call a method in Java?",
      "correctAnswer": "toUpperCase()",
      "options": ["(methodName);","methodName;","methodName();","methodName[];"]
    }
  ],
  "metadata": {
      "quiz_length": 10
  }
}
